The day I was born ,
goats wailed like crazy .
And that day ,
a demon was born with me .
1999 , YEONGWOL , GANGWON-DO
After hiding in my mom 's womb for ten months ,
it came into the world ten minutes before I did .
That thing lived by eating the flesh of my leg .
Yes , the baby is coming out !
Push ! You have to push !
Hold her legs down . Push !
- Try to relax . - Here it comes !
Here . Take a deep breath . One more time .
- This one is okay . - The clamp .
- It 's just her leg . - The gauze too .
- Pass me a towel . - Sure .
Hold the baby . And tie this right here .
Pass it over .
That one ...
won 't make it .
It won 't live long .
People said
it should 've been killed back then .
My mom died a week after we were born ,
and I was told that my dad died in a car accident a month after that .
That 's what my grandpa told me when I entered middle school .
And ...
the doctor was wrong .
2014 , YEONGWOL , GANGWON-DO
That thing didn 't die that quickly .
It 's still alive .
Fuck .
That family moved here recently .
I heard they sell dogs .
I rarely see them though .
Anyway , that family is weird .
When did they move here ?
About a month ago , I guess ?
And when did your cattle start acting up ?
About three weeks ago .
We 're almost there . It 's that house over there .
God , those goddamn dogs bark and howl all day long .
It 's so bizarre ...
It feels colder here . The sound of the wind ...
Aren 't I right ?
Gosh .
They obviously don 't want to come out .
This is no joke . This energy is ...
Look at this .
There 's something unusual .
Let go !
People have told me that ...
- Something 's fishy . - Otherwise ...
You know ? Why aren 't they coming out ?
Ma 'am , let 's come back tomorrow .
We are
living with the demon like this .
Oh , dear Lord .
Please ...
Please forgive me for my sins .
I beg you with all my heart and soul .
Please forgive me !
Come here for a second .
Why ?
Come here .
Have you been doing well in school ?
Have you made friends ?
This time , we 'll try to hold out so that we won 't have to move again .
I bet you hate it so much .
What ?
Your leg .
And that thing .
- Your twin sister - - - What about it ?
I didn 't even register her birth .
I didn 't teach her to talk , but I should 've at least - -
Forget it . I understand .
Geum-hwa , you see ...
I had no idea she 'd live this long .
She scares me .
I 'm still terrified .
Every night ,
the sound of her crying ...
I am so wondrously saved from sin
Jesus so sweetly abides within
There at the cross where he took me in
- Glory to his name - You hear that , right ?
Yes .
Hymn number 250 .
- Glory to his name - " Down at the Cross . "
Shit .
Down where for cleansing from sin I cried
Listen carefully .
That can 't be a person crying , right ?
Here , this way .
It sounds like a kid crying .
The bush clover branch .
All spirits of the earth and sky .
Princess .
I came to say hello .
Princess ?
Evil is nothing special .
These charlatans you see here are evil .
These fake prophets that you see here
are also known as cults . It is reported that the total number
of cult-related incidents per year reaches 1,200 ,
and the total number of victims exceeds 50,000 .
In this country , where freedom of religion is rather overly protected ,
our research institute is the only organization
at the vanguard of this spiritual war .
Please show us your support .
Support this good cause .
- Okay . - Okay .
I 'd like to thank Pastor Kim Tae-sik
from Seoul Theological University for inviting me today .
And lastly , the most important thing .
Faith .
WHERE TO SEND YOUR DONATIONS
Our research institute is in dire need of your faith and support .
Try to imagine how Jesus must 've felt while climbing Golgotha
all alone .
Please support us . Please pray for us .
We 'll be the salt and light of the world .
Park Ung-jae is a crook !
- He 's a crook ! - He 's a crook !
Resign as pastor !
- Resign ! - Resign !
Stop your witch hunt !
- Stop it now ! - Stop it now !
Park Ung-jae must be ousted !
Shut down his research institute !
- Shut it down ! - Shut it down !
Stop the human rights violation !
- Stop it ! - Stop it !
- Brethren , let 's raise our hands - Brethren , let 's raise our hands
- Make a vow to the Lord - Make a vow to the Lord
Over there ! It 's Park Ung-jae !
- Where ? - Where is he ?
- There ! - Get him !
- Get lost ! - Get lost !
Jeez , eggs aren 't cheap . What 's wrong with those women ?
Why throw food at someone ?
- I told you to be careful . - Gosh !
You shouldn 't have messed with Agape Convent .
Jeez , my trench coat ...
Pastor , you 're becoming more popular by the day .
That 's right . Thank goodness my dear fans are all ladies this time .
- He bought a new coat again . - Gosh .
FAR EASTERN RELIGION RESEARCH INSTITUTE
AGAPE WELFARE CENTER EXECUTIVE DIRECTOR JEONG GI-EUN
EVIL NUNS BEHIND THE FACADE OF CATHOLICISM
SPIRITUAL MOTHER PARK GEUM-JI PRAYER SERVICE FOR IMMORTAL LIFE
MOSES WILL JUDGE THE WORLD
Gosh .
Our heating bill was 500,000 won , but I can 't keep the windows closed .
Who doesn 't have an air purifier these days ?
- I 've been saying ... - Deaconess Sim ,
has the Methodist church paid us ?
You 'll have to finish the article quickly for us to get paid .
He never finishes what he starts . He 's all talk .
- Deaconess Sim , I feel suffocated . - What pastor chain-smokes all day long ?
- I can 't breathe . - He 's such a slacker .
- All he does is buy designer clothes . - I 'm off to Gangwon-do .
Are you going there because of Deer Hill ?
Of course . Do you think I 'm going on a vacation ?
- He 's spreading himself too thin . - Jeez .
Finish the article on the Moses Adventists first - -
Gosh , Deaconess Sim .
Step by step , okay ?
Even if we expose them now , the Church can 't even sue them .
Then what about Agape Convent ?
I 've already uploaded that one . Send it to Catholic Digest tomorrow .
The title should be ...
" Mysterious nuns
who can even cure cancer . "
End it with a question mark instead of an exclamation mark .
Jeez , how cheesy .
Come on . It needs the commercial appeal .
Just hurry back and finish the article and the overdue columns ...
Deaconess Sim .
You see , with Buddhist organizations ,
the amount of money jumps to another level .
Let 's go on a vacation to Phuket this winter .
Sounds good ? Separately .
Also ,
you wanted an air purifier .
- Amen . - An air purifier !
- Amen . - We 'll buy an air purifier !
Amen !
All right . Attention , everyone .
What flower is this ?
- Lotus flower . - Lotus flower .
Correct .
It 's a sacred flower .
Even though it grows in muddy , murky water ,
this beautiful flower always rises out of the dirty water , completely unstained .
Everyone .
This world is one big muddy mess ,
and it 's becoming even more dangerous and cruel .
However , our prayers and sincerity will change the world .
All right .
Then we 'll pray for the typhoon victims in Jinju
before we wrap up .
- The General protects us . - The General protects us .
- Thank you . - Thank you .
All right , thanks . See you tomorrow .
You should eat proper meals . Jeez .
Can you up the expense budget , then ?
Spend it first and submit all the receipts to Deaconess Sim .
You always say that .
By the way , how come there 's nothing catchy ?
- Is what you sent me really everything ? - Yes , that 's it .
What does your gut tell you ?
Come on . It 's not like you 're an amateur .
- Amen . - Anything ?
One odd thing is ...
that there 's nothing odd .
What about its doctrine ? Does it stem from Donghak ?
No .
Dangun ?
- Guan Yu ? - No , not at all .
It 's actually more classic than I expected .
It 's strongly influenced by Buddhism and Esoteric Buddhism , but it 's pure .
They don 't even collect offerings .
They actually give alms to believers who are struggling financially .
They give alms ?
You fool , then it 's a full network . It 's a pyramid scheme .
No , it 's not .
Well , a new cult . Adultery and money laundering .
So , it 's a network . What else ?
If I were to tell you something that 's off ...
Pastor , don 't Buddhists worship Buddha or bodhisattvas ?
Yes , that 's right .
But these people worship someone they call " General . "
At both chapters .
That 's not what I 'm after .
I need something scandalous . Something shocking and obscene .
I 'll come up with a scenario to present to the monks at the headquarters .
Mr. Go , let 's dig a little deeper .
Bring me something juicy .
Bring it over here .
Did you call forensics ?
You cannot be here . Please stand outside the police line .
- You made it , sir . - Yes .
Why didn 't you answer my calls ?
Hey , what 's all this fuss about at this early hour ?
Hey !
I told you guys not to touch it .
We have to preserve the scene .
Get out ! Captain Hwang is here .
- Damn it . - Hello , Captain Hwang .
Call Forensics and find out where they are now .
- Yes , sir . - A truck crashed into this - -
What is this ?
It didn 't rot at all . It 's completely dried up .
This construction job must 've been done pretty recently .
Yes , this won 't be a hard case .
I 've already contacted construction companies .
- It 's pretty small . - Pardon me ?
The height . It 's short .
The victim was a middle schooler at the most .
While investigating the Moses Adventists ' Gangwon HQ ,
I coincidentally discovered this new religion influenced by Buddhism .
They have two chapters , in Taebaek and Jeongseon .
At the moment , the total number of believers is just under 50 .
Most of them are teachers , nurses ,
- or civil servants - - - Mr . Park .
I bet there are about 3,000 propagation centers like that .
- I don 't see anything problematic with - - - Venerable sir , just a moment .
Do you know what alarms me the most ?
This organization , Deer Hill ,
doesn 't make any profit off its believers .
Why does that alarm you ?
I 'm sure you know the Japanese cult Aum Shinrikyo .
The culprit of the subway gas attack .
Do you know what they started out as ?
A yoga organization .
They sponsored various organizations .
Then later on , the leader , Shoko Asahara , started talking Buddhist doctrines ,
saying " I 'm Buddha . I 'm God . "
Then what happened ?
Isn 't it so predictable ?
Doomsday .
" Doomsday is near . We shall let everything go and go to heaven . "
That incident killed so many people .
When that happens , it 'll be too late .
Control them by finding their unlawful deeds
and contradicting doctrines ,
or people will criticize you for letting them
dishonor your association as well as the Buddha - -
Pastor Park Ung-jae , thank you for letting us know .
I think it 's a bit of a stretch to call it a new religion .
It looks like a small organization founded for socializing or welfare purposes .
You probably don 't know this ,
but seeking harmonious coexistence is key - -
Venerable sir .
I 've been doing this for over a decade now .
Nowadays , Protestant and Catholic churches are very concerned
- with purifying - - - Listen .
Such notion of Christian dichotomy won 't help you find the Noble Truths .
Sir .
A propagation center in Chungju was recently on In Depth 60 Minutes
for selling Buddha statues and memorial tablets , you know .
It wouldn 't be a bad idea to clamp down on them in advance .
Why does that octopus head hate me so much ?
Ung-jae , you totally sounded like a salesman .
Come on . A salesman ? Seriously ?
That octopus head controls our money .
Try to get on his good side .
It 's for a good cause , so let 's take the easy route .
What the hell is this ?
Give me information on that organization , Deer Hill .
What for ?
I 'll give you an idea .
- What are the three elements of religion ? - Leader , believers , and scriptures .
If it 's a newly-risen religion , they must have their own scriptures .
If they use their own interpretations or go by a disapproved version - -
Only then will your association have grounds to impose sanctions on them .
Bingo .
Homage to AvalokiteÅ  vara .
- Good work today . - Thank you .
A body was found inside a concrete wall of an underpass
near Yeongwol , Gangwon-do on the 18th ,
and the police are currently investigating the case .
The body that was found is speculated to be
a student of Donggang Girls ' Middle School with the surname , Park .
The police have requested an autopsy to determine the exact cause of death
and are closing in on suspects by investigating construction companies ...
DOGYE RESTAURANT SUNDAE , OX BLOOD
Cheol-jin , why are you so late ?
You should eat something too .
Come have a seat .
You should 've told me that your friend was coming over .
We don 't have many side dishes .
Gwangmok , I knew you 'd visit me .
I 'm happy I got to see you .
It 's been so long .
I 'm a failure .
I failed to protect Father . I 'm hiding like this because I 'm a coward .
No , that 's not true . I just think
that your mother 's warm home-cooked meal
might have made you weak-willed .
I was afraid .
Every night , they ...
The dead kids come at me .
Gwangmok , it 's strange . Something ...
Something 's gone wrong .
Jiguk .
We 're fighting against evil at the moment .
We 're carrying out our divine mission .
We mustn 't let our fears or regrets bog us down . You know that .
Jeungjang also reached Nirvana following Damun , you know ?
Right .
Go ahead and die .
The world will call you soon .
" You blood-soaked beast , stop crying .
Raise your head and look at the light .
Kneel down . "
- " Wipe your tears and behold the Truth . - " Wipe your tears and behold the Truth .
- Pain is the fruit of faith . - Pain is the fruit of faith .
- Pain purifies your blood , - Pain purifies your blood ,
- which will enlighten this world . - which will enlighten this world .
- Do not fear , beasts of the dark . - Do not fear , beasts of the dark .
- You will defeat evil . - You will defeat evil .
- You shall catch the snake - You shall catch the snake
- on the fundament . " - on the fundament . "
- Adzuki beans ? - Yes .
From the corpse from the underpass .
I found quite a bit of it in her mouth and esophagus .
Well , it is edible . It 's nothing too strange , right ?
Right , but ...
I also found some odd-looking talisman with the beans .
And I think there was
a similar case from a while ago .
We 're deers
with pure hearts .
Also ,
evil that threatens good certainly exists in this world .
Disciple Seo Ji-yeong lost her mother
in a car accident recently .
In addition ,
Disciple Kim Ji-hyeon 's husband was in a big accident .
If ...
the DUI driver
and the lazy site manager ...
Had they never been born ,
such tragic accidents wouldn 't have happened .
The light and darkness of this world are connected .
Because darkness exists ,
those who protect the light can shine even more brightly .
Deer Hill 's scriptures
foretell the beings that protect the light
- in detail . - Yes , scriptures .
As you all know ,
- our scriptures are holy books . - Gosh , my stomach ...
There are only four copies .
" Chae , hidden in the dazzling river , listen .
You are a beast .
You are a bloodstained beast .
The world will only see your darkness , so do not be sad ... "
Let 's see . Scriptures .
At the end of the scripture ,
there is a prophecy that 81 evil enemies with impure energy
will be born on this land .
I see , " 81 evil enemies . "
- Goodness . - In our scriptures , they 're described ...
- Now , we know the genre . - ... as snakes .
They 're born evil .
The beings that threaten the good energy in the world ...
You should be on standby here . You two , follow me .
Check everyone who comes out .
Hey , let 's go .
Hello , I 'm Detective Jo Myeong-hwan from Yeongwol Police Station .
Is there a man named Kim Cheol-jin here ?
What is this about ?
We 're looking for the suspect of a murder case of a student .
His name is Kim Cheol-jin .
This is his address in the system at the moment , but ...
- What 's going on ? - You came to the wrong place .
This is just a Buddhist sanctuary .
It does look like that , but ...
ID everyone who 's here now
- and take a look inside . - Yes , sir .
- Excuse us . Please cooperate . - Actually , just check their IDs .
It looks like a fake address .
You idiot , isn 't it obvious ?
I figured that out right away .
Damn it .
Shit .
Hey , what 's up ?
Yes , we 're wrapping up here .
God damn it .
Good day , sir .
Do I know you ?
Oh , I 'm investigating this propagation center .
I 'm Park Ung-jae .
Oh , I 've seen you on TV .
You 're better-looking in person .
By the way , what brings you here ?
- Oh , it 's ... - Captain .
We got the address of Kim Cheol-jin 's mother .
- You 're sure this time , right ? - Yes .
Let 's go !
Have a nice day .
Kim Cheol-jin ?
Go ahead and die .
And as for your karma ,
I shall take it away .
GEUMGANG UNIVERSITY
About that organization , Deer Hill ...
The ones in Taebaek and Jeongseon aren 't their only chapters .
- There 's another one ? - Jecheon .
- That deer logo . - Oh , you 're right .
And this is in Danyang . You see the same logo .
How did you find out that they have other chapters ?
Because ...
there should be two more .
Now , let 's take a look at what you had .
This portrait of the General in Taebaek .
Also , this altar portrait in Jeongseon .
What about them ?
They are ...
not generals .
They 're the Four Great Heavenly Kings , who symbolize the cardinal directions .
- The Four Heavenly Kings . - Correct .
In Esoteric Buddhism , they 're called ShitennÅ  .
The four guardians that protect the Buddha .
They 're portraits of the two of them .
First , let 's look at the painting at the Deer Hill chapter in Taebaek .
Below him , there are two servants .
On the right , you see Gandharva , albeit small .
And on the left , you see Pishacha under him .
This blue-faced god holding the pipa .
It 's King Jiguk , the guardian of the eastern direction .
And the one in Jeongseon is King Damun .
A Yaksha and a Rakshasa are his followers .
He holds a small pagoda in his left hand and a spear in his right hand .
He is the guardian of the northern direction .
All right , this map will shed light on their secret .
King Jiguk in Taebaek , which is east .
King Damun in Jeongseon , which is north .
From there , we can map out the four cardinal points .
That gives us two more locations .
- Jecheon , which is west . - King Gwangmok .
- Danyang , which is south . - King Jeungjang .
Look at you . My alumnus , Lee Jeong-beom , from Whimoon High School .
All the temple food sure has sharpened your insight .
I eat at the cafeteria these days .
- Ung-jae , by the way ... - Good . This is great .
A new religious group that worships such deities .
Have you seen it before ?
No , I 've never seen anything like this before .
The Four Heavenly Kings
were originally evil spirits in India .
However , they meet the Buddha and become devoted to his teachings .
Hence , they become gods that protect the world from evil , malicious spirits .
Evil gods that fight evil spirits ...
Shit , jeez .
Scriptures , where are you ?
Yo-sep !
Pastor , go on in .
You should go in .
- Jeez , go on in . - Shit .
Someone must live in this room .
Kim Cheol-jin .
Pastor !
Scriptures about King Jiguk ...
The suspect is here . He 's going up .
Wait for your cue .
Mom , listen carefully to what I 'm about to say .
Regardless of what people say , what you see isn 't everything .
Your son
fought against evil
for this world .
I 'm sure God will appreciate all the hard work I 've done .
I was blessed as your son .
Mom , when we meet again in heaven ,
- I will ... - He 's on the rooftop !
- Fuck ! - Quickly !
- He 's on the rooftop ! - Hey , go !
I will give you a big hug .
Hey , hurry !
Under the merciful smile of the Buddha ...
Found him !
The beast finally wins the war against the snakes .
The skies will never forget your hard work .
- Hey , Kim Cheol-jin ! - Behold .
- You bastard ! - Now , with the wings that he has earned ,
- the beast will be - The beast will be
- born again . - born again .
- Hey , don 't ! - Get down ! Damn it !
- No ! - Kim Cheol-jin !
The suspect jumped .
SEOUL NAMDAEMUN POLICE STATION
MURDER SUSPECT HANGS HIMSELF AND JUMPS TO DEATH
Hey , here 's information on Kim Cheol-jin .
Thanks , sister .
Whatever , you smooth talker . Don 't ask me for such favors from now on .
You think I 'm a pushover ?
Come on . I helped you with the Sion Group case a while back .
Have you forgotten ?
I help you too . We have to help each other out .
Hey , it 's the holiday season . Christmas is coming up .
Do you know how sensitive everyone is now ?
Hello ?
Yes .
I 'm outside .
I 'll be back very soon , okay ?
Yangju Juvenile Detention Center ?
Kim Cheol-jin committed a murder when he was a minor .
GANGWON PROVINCIAL OFFICE OF EDUCATION
- Hello . - Hello .
Jiguk had asked me to get this .
I looked into it , and it seems like the family has moved around quite a bit .
The records from this school are probably the most recent records .
Thank you , Bodhisattva .
Gwangmok .
I 'm honored to finally meet you in person .
STUDENT RECORDS LEE GEUM-HWA
The East Seoul-bound bus will be arriving shortly .
This isn 't an express bus . It will stop in Jecheon and Wonju on the way ,
so please check your ticket prior to boarding .
Down at the cross where my savior died
Down where for cleansing from sin I cried
There to my heart was the blood applied
Glory to his name
RANDOM CHAT I 'LL VISIT SOON , I 'M SERIOUS
YOU CAN STAY WITH ME HAVE YOU BEEN TO SEOUL ?
YES , EVERLAND
YOU MORON , THAT 'S NOT SEOUL
I 'M ACTUALLY A MORON
SEND ME A PHOTO
Why did you lock your door ?
Because I 'm scared .
Did you feed her ?
Did you give her food ?
- No . - Take some food to her now .
The King Jiguk scripture you brought from Taebaek
is basically early Buddhist literature
mixed with The Samdhinirmocana Sutra and The Diamond Sutra .
But the important thing is ,
there 's a sutra I 've never seen before .
It 's the part at the very end .
It 's called Hangmagyeong .
- " Hangma . " - That 's right .
As you can guess , it 's about gods fighting against evil enemies .
It 's like The Book of Revelation .
Listen to this .
Other parts of the scripture are written in an overly practical manner ,
but Hangmagyeong is very symbolic .
Like the Revelation to John from the Bible .
- What could it be ? - Have you heard of " hangma " before ?
No , never .
Shouldn 't you know about it after all this time ?
You should call it a day .
Are you wearing makeup ?
Deaconess Sim , he is ...
He 's a monk .
No , they 're perfect for each other .
" The sad beasts lying face down will be born again with wings
and trample all over the snakes on the fundament .
Beasts , who protect the light . Stars , who will trample over the snakes .
Wipe your tears . Do not hide your trembling body .
Catch the snake nestling in the girl 's body .
Those snakes will have beautiful eyes and sweet tongues .
Brave beasts , do not look at their eyes .
Do not listen to their words .
Only the snakes ' blood will purify you . "
Mister .
Na-han .
Na-han , you need to wake up .
" Under the merciful smile of the Buddha ,
four beasts will win the war against the snakes
and shall be born again .
The Buddha 's bright light will protect you . "
So we were right .
They do worship the Four Heavenly Kings .
That 's right .
Have a look at this .
It was originally a beast .
But it meets the Buddha and starts following his teachings .
- And here - - - Then it becomes a god that fights evil ,
ascends to heaven and eventually becomes the Buddha .
These folks ...
They 're after ghosts .
Haean , can you find out who wrote this scripture ?
There 's a Buddhist name written on the last page .
Kim Pungsa .
Kim Pungsa ?
Kim Pungsa ...
Ask Dr. Goo .
Dr. Goo ? Who 's Dr. Goo ?
Google .
Deaconess Sim , are you trying to charm us with your sense of humor ?
My goodness .
I should give you a raise ! My gosh .
Buddhism , religion .
Nice , look at that . This is so much better .
" Tibetan Buddhist Master , Nechung Tenpa ,
wishes to meet the founder of Dongbanggyo , Kim Je-seok . "
" Dongbanggyo " ?
It 's that man , Kim Je-seok .
Yes , he was very famous in the Buddhist community .
He still has many followers .
The founder of Dongbanggyo , Kim Je-seok , wrote this scripture ?
I know someone who 's an expert on Dongbanggyo .
Who ?
The octopus .
Monk Octopus is quite materialistic .
I 'll call him and give him a heads-up . Make sure you buy something good .
God , that octopus ...
Why does he live in the mountains , not in the ocean ?
I see cars up here .
Thank you for such a valuable gift .
How thoughtful .
I know that monks like to keep their material possessions to a minimum .
- Just as a sincere gesture ... - Thank you .
A sincere gesture that 's worth 6,000 won , right ?
I spoke to Monk Haean briefly on the phone .
- I see . - Kim Je-seok of Dongbanggyo ...
DONGBANGGYO
The first thing I 'd like to say is ...
Pungsa Kim Je-seok
is real .
What do you mean ?
In short ,
he 's become a god .
Conservative Buddhist organizations disapproved of him back then ,
but Kim Je-seok has attained Buddhahood .
Here 's a photo of him .
It was taken around 1940 .
Because he was incredibly enlightened , Esoteric Buddhist monks from Japan
and even the governor-general called him Master .
So , he was pro-Japanese ?
I 'm not done yet .
Oh , my apologies .
He actually sent money to the Heroic Corps to help them raise the independence fund .
Even after gaining independence ,
he retrieved the assets and treasures that Japan had stolen from us .
However ,
when the political turbulence began escalating ,
he started spending everything for the religious community and welfare .
And naturally , he was able to expand his influence .
So , that 's Dongbanggyo .
Bingo .
Then in 1985 ,
Kim Je-seok suddenly disbanded Dongbanggyo and disappeared .
Why did he do that ?
I heard he was planning to write new scriptures .
- Have you met him in person ? - No .
Only few people got to meet him in person .
I heard only his closest disciples were allowed to meet with him .
Would he be alive now ?
I 'm not sure .
Kim Je-seok is from Yeongwol , Gangwon-do .
He was born in 1899 , so he should be ...
He should be 116 years old .
Then he probably passed away .
Unfortunately .
Pastor , here .
Yes , I saw it .
DONGBANGGYO FOUNDER , KIM JE-SEOK ,
DONATES TO YANGJU JUVENILE DETENTION CENTER
Right , sir .
It 's getting cold , and Christmas is just around the corner ,
so I suddenly thought of the boys at the detention center .
Okay , I 'll see you soon .
You don 't think he 's still alive , right ?
He should be dead now , if he was fake .
- But you know what , Yo-sep ? - Yes ?
Aren 't you curious ?
About what ?
What if , somewhere in the world ,
the real one really exists ...
Pastor , what are you talking about ? God is alive .
God is alive ?
A friend of mine
graduated from the seminary , got married ,
and moved to South Africa for missionary work .
He always prayed diligently .
They were a couple with a strong faith .
But a few years later , he moved back all by himself .
Why ?
His entire family , except him , was shot to death .
Including his two-year-old son
and his newborn ...
His newborn daughter as well . They all died .
Do you know what the culprit , a 13-year-old Muslim boy , said ?
He said it was God 's will .
You see , I still feel so clueless .
We 're struggling and scuffling at rock bottom like ants .
Where is our God ? And what is he doing ?
So , I 'd like to meet that man at least .
People say that he 's become a god .
UPHOLD THE LAW WITH FAITH AND REFORM WITH FAITH
It 's noisy here . Let 's go inside .
Sure .
- A religion research institute ? - Yes .
What inspired you to bring gifts for our boys ?
I just wanted to meet the boys
and show my gratitude for all your hard work and service .
That 's not the impression I 'm getting .
- Pastor . - Yes .
I 've been working here for 30 years .
No one donates or helps without an agenda .
Do whatever it is you came here to do and leave . It 's okay .
Gosh , you 're very straightforward .
Years ago , Dong ...
- Dongbanggyo . - Right , Dongbanggyo .
I heard they donated to this detention center .
Oh , that was about 20 years ago .
Right , we built this training facility , Jeseok Hall , with their donation .
I see . Then the name , Jeseok Hall , must be from
the name of Dongbanggyo 's founder , Pungsa Kim Je-seok .
Right , yes .
At one point ,
the religious community targeted him , but he was such a wonderful person .
He thought of our boys as his own sons .
I see . Why do you think he did that ?
Pardon me ?
You said no one donates or helps without an agenda .
Master Kim did everything in his power
to support and care for these four inmates in this photo .
Four inmates ?
Four inmates that killed their own fathers .
Educating them had its limits .
Hence , through the power of religion ...
Master Kim went beyond that . He even adopted them .
All four of them ?
And one of them was Kim Cheol-jin , right ?
Yes . What a beautiful story , right ?
He wanted to be a father who they could look up to .
Then ,
the rest of them , these three boys .
Could you tell me who they are ?
Jeong Na-han , Kim Cheol-jin , Chae Tae-geun , and Jeon Sang-beom .
All four of them are mentioned in the scripture .
" Chae , hidden in the dazzling river , listen .
You are a beast . You are a bloodstained beast .
The world will only see your darkness , so do not be sad . "
It totally checks out .
" Dazzling river . " It 's " Gwangju " based on the Chinese characters .
Chae . This is referring to Chae Tae-geun , who was born in Gwangju .
And " Jeong " in " the river of stars . "
Seongju . The Seongju Jeong clan , Jeong Na-han .
" Blue river . "
The Cheongju Kim clan , Kim Cheol-jin .
" The river of thunder . " Jinju .
" Jeon , the hidden beast " ?
The Jinju Jeon clan , Jeon Sang-beom .
This scripture accurately predicted everything .
The four boys from prison .
And three of them died .
What ?
Three of them died ? What do you mean ?
Here , look .
Look at the Heavenly King portraits in Jeongseon and Danyang .
You see halos above their heads , right ?
Halos .
Catholic martyrs are also depicted with halos above their heads .
I was curious as well .
Why do you think only the ones in Jeongseon and Danyang have halos ?
It means they 're dead .
They attained Nirvana .
Gracefully , while catching ghosts .
Gosh , no way .
All right . Now that Kim Cheol-jin is also dead ,
King Jiguk in Taebaek needs a halo above his head as well .
Then that means ...
this guy is the only one that 's left .
King Gwangmok in Jecheon .
JECHEON , GWANGMOK
SEOUL NAMDAEMUN POLICE STATION
So , three out of the four guys actually died .
First off , as for Jeon Sang-beom ...
He died in the Yeongwol Maria Postnatal Care Center fire ?
Gosh , many mothers and babies died in this fire .
And it says here that Chae Tae-geun died in Canada .
He was convicted of robbery and murder .
He killed a Korean-Canadian family on the spur of the moment
and got caught while on the run .
He hanged himself at a detention center in Toronto .
Jeez , this invalidates the correlation I thought they had .
How about the last one who 's still alive , Jeong Na-han ?
PERSONAL RECORDS JEONG NA-HAN
Born in 1983 . Name , Jeong Na-han .
I vaguely remember him .
A middle school boy , who grew up
in a red-light district , beat his father to death .
His mother must 've worked in the red-light district .
And I bet his father was human trash , a pimp or something like that .
It 's obvious , you know .
There were a lot of disagreements as to how
this middle schooler should be punished or treated .
I remember there were many controversies .
In a way ,
I feel bad for him .
He doesn 't deserve your pity .
My baby , my white ram lamb
Fall asleep in Mama 's arms
The cold winter
The cold winter storm
- Stay far away from our house - Stay far away from our house
- Dark nights , go away - Dark nights , go away
Hushaby , my baby
Don 't cry , hushaby
Stay far away from our house
King Gwangmok .
He 's better-looking in person .
NOKYAWON
Gwangmok is here .
Hello .
They say that deers are immortal .
Why are they so weak though ?
Death is not the end , you know .
It 'll be reincarnated as a human being .
Right .
But why is it that all creatures
have such sad eyes when they die ?
I saw it with my own eyes .
It can 't be a human being .
Gwangmok .
The beings that we 're after don 't look like that .
I know that better than anyone else does .
" Those snakes will have beautiful eyes
and sweet tongues .
Catch the snake nestling in the girl 's body . "
The Demon also appeared before the Buddha looking beautiful .
Do not let it fool you .
That girl is the snake .
Master .
Gwangmok is here .
He 's deteriorating by the day . We don 't have time .
" Beast , listen .
The day the snake sheds its first blood ,
the light will go off ,
and darkness will befall this world . "
You must hurry .
You 're the only one that 's left now .
Listen , Jeong in the river of stars .
You are Gwangmok .
From now on , your name will be Gwangmok .
" Gwang " means " wide , " and " mok " means " to see . "
You are a brave general who destroys all evil spirits in the west .
You will become a star .
You will become my star ,
a star that illuminates the world .
I will protect you no matter what
so that you can achieve dharma
and enlighten this dark world of suffering .
He says that he loves you .
I 've served him all my life as his disciple ,
but I have yet to hear him say that to me .
Who are you ?
What brings you here ?
This is a restricted area .
Well , I somehow ended up here .
I 'm sorry , but you must leave the premises .
Okay , I apologize .
Wait .
Will you jump over the fence again ?
Exit through the gate . I 'll open it for you .
Okay .
What the ...
" Lee Geum-hwa " ?
What ?
Hey , wait !
Darn it .
PESTICIDE MEZORAN
Please hear me out .
Captain Hwang .
This is huge .
I 'm sure there 's something .
You keep spewing utter nonsense .
The Kim Cheol-jin case too .
There 's a reason behind all of this .
So what 's the reason , then ?
Kim Cheol-jin was a murderer and an ex-convict ,
and the other people are just ...
They 're just normal people . Stop making such a fuss .
Gosh !
What normal person
has an elephant at home ?
And what normal person drives into your car just because you tailed him ?
This isn 't our jurisdiction . Contact Wonju Police Station .
Well ...
Shouldn 't we at least find out the reason ? No ?
Wait , Captain Hwang !
" The beast will trample over the snakes
on the fundament of the light and win the war .
The number of the 81 snakes that will harm the inextinguishable light is as follows . "
The number of the snakes and the light .
Pastor , this " light " that keeps coming up in this scripture ...
In Buddhism , light symbolizes Maitreya .
Lord Maitreya , the future Buddha .
Like the Messiah in Christianity .
The Four Heavenly Kings protect the Maitreya
from the snakes .
Then the snakes are probably like Satan in the Bible .
Ung-jae , there is no concept of absolute evil in Buddhism .
No , that 's not true .
There was Mara Papiya , who seduced the Buddha .
Also , Asura and Mara in other scriptures ...
- They 're all evil - - - No , you got it all wrong .
They 're all biases based on Christian beliefs .
From Mara Papiya to Asura , if you trace their etymological roots ,
you 'll learn they 're just expressions of human desires and obsession .
You can call that " evil " if you wish .
Whatever , smarty-pants .
Ung-jae , I 'll call you back later .
It 's so hectic here now because of our Christmas event .
Why is Christmas such a big deal to you , Buddhist monks ?
We host one of our biggest annual events on Christmas .
Every Christmas , the Tibetan Buddhist master ,
Nechung Tenpa , visits Korea as our representative .
A Tibetan Buddhist master ? Why ?
To pay his respects .
He congratulates the cardinal at Myeongdong Cathedral .
Before that , he always visits our HQ
and holds a service . The thing is ...
Ung-jae , he 's here .
All right , I 'll call you later .
A Tibetan Buddhist master ...
This is what came up in our search . Dr. Goo , remember ?
" Year 1985 , the greatest Buddhist prophet . "
Then in 1985 ,
Kim Je-seok suddenly disbanded Dongbanggyo and disappeared .
That 's it .
He must 've started writing the scriptures after meeting Nechung Tenpa .
Seven , one , seven , four , five , three .
- Two , eight , one , seven ... - Hey , baldy . Pick up already .
What he learned from practicing asceticism
is that pain changes as well .
That can exist for there is this .
That can be born for this was born .
That will be destroyed for this is destroyed .
We 're off to Seoul now .
Kim Je-seok ?
Maitreya .
Thank you . Thank you very much .
It 's going to be okay .
MERRY CHRISTMAS
There is no concept of absolute evil in Buddhism .
Pungsa Kim Je-seok ...
You 'll learn they 're just expressions of human desires and obsession .
... is real .
He 's become a god .
That can exist for there is this . That can be born for this was born .
That will be destroyed for this is destroyed .
RESIDENT REGISTRATION NUMBER
Everyone seems so excited about Christmas .
Yo-sep !
Is Christmas a joyous day ?
It 's a happy day , of course . It 's the day when Jesus was born .
I 've always thought about this on every Christmas .
It 's actually a very sad day .
What do you mean ?
So many babies in Bethlehem lost their lives for Jesus to be born
because Herod heard from the Magi that the king of the Jews had been born .
" When Herod realized that he had been outwitted by the Magi ,
he was furious , and he gave orders to kill all the boys
in Bethlehem and its vicinity who were two years old and under ... "
The Gospel of Matthew , 2 : 16 .
Mister .
The thing is ...
" Those snakes will have beautiful eyes and sweet tongues . "
- I don 't care about dying , - " Do not listen to their words . "
but can I at least know the reason ?
Why do I have to die ?
Jecheon in the west , Taebaek in the east , Jeongseon in the north ,
and Danyang in the south .
There was a center point .
Kim Je-seok 's hometown .
Yeongwol .
In the same spot , the snake that will harm the light is born 100 years later .
Kim Je-seok was born in Yeongwol in 1899 , right ?
And 100 years after that ...
Year 1999 .
He believed that something born in Yeongwol would end up harming him .
And ...
" The day the snake sheds its first blood .
The snake nestling in the girl 's body . "
MURDER SUSPECT COMMITS SUICIDE
Those who were born in Yeongwol in 1999 .
RESIDENT REGISTRATION NUMBER
Girls .
You were born evil .
And death is not the end .
It 's a new beginning .
Rest in this sunny spot .
I 'll pray with all my heart
that you 'll be born as Buddha in your next life .
What now ?
Captain Hwang , please trust me and look up the records .
Wasn 't the girl Kim Cheol-jin killed born in Yeongwol in 1999 ?
Dude , seriously . Enough is enough - -
Look up the records , please !
Jeon Sang-beom , from the same juvie ,
was the culprit behind the arson case in Yeongwol in 1999 .
Chae Tae-geun , the robbery and murder convict , killed himself in Canada .
Most of the victims killed by these guys
were girls who were born in Yeongwol in 1999 .
REGARDING THE BEANS AUTOPSY REPORT
For over a decade , they 've been killing girls and staging them as accidents .
For some , right after birth .
They even chased those who had moved to another country .
Hold on .
Then I have a favor to ask of you .
There really is a demon that lives at my place .
She 's my twin sister .
She was born with me ,
so she 's evil too , right ?
Kill her as well .
So she can be born again .
For her to be born as a human being in her next life .
Detective Jo .
Kids who were born in 1999 . What grade are they in this year ?
Let 's see . My niece is in seventh grade now , so ...
They 're in ninth grade this year .
Find out
how many female ninth graders reside in Yeongwol at the moment .
About the numbers , there are 81 rows in total .
Look .
Ninety nine ,
two .
Pastor , these are
resident registration numbers .
I thought they looked like resident registration numbers ,
but I wondered why there were only ten digits .
The birth year and the seventh digit , which indicates the sex .
Those are set , so get rid of them and ...
Ten .
That 's why the scriptures were completed in 2000 .
After checking all girls ' resident registration numbers .
All girls who were born in Yeongwol in 1999 .
There are 81 in total .
Hence , the " 81 evil enemies . "
There are three all girls ' middle schools .
If I add up all girls in ninth grade ...
There are 38 .
Oh , that 's it ?
Then what about eighth graders ?
Eighth graders ...
There are 87 in total .
What about seventh graders ?
There are 79 .
MISSING JANG HUI-SEON , BORN IN 1999
Lord .
Our God .
Deliver us from our enemies
and defend us from them that rise up against us .
Deliver us from the workers of iniquity
and save us from bloody men .
They lie and wait for our souls .
The mighty are gathered against us .
Oh , Lord .
This is neither for our transgression
nor for our sin .
KIM BO-MI , AGE 3 , BORN IN 1999
They run and prepare themselves
without our fault .
Lord .
Awake to help us
and behold .
Do not hide your face from us .
Do not turn your servants away in anger .
You have been our helper .
God , our savior .
Do not reject us
or forsake us .
Son , what took you so long ?
It took way too long .
Who are you ?
I am the wailing one .
I have been waiting for you .
Hurry .
Too much blood has been shed .
Do you see it ?
Can 't you feel it ?
I am your sustenance .
Open your heart .
I shall choose you .
Hushaby , my baby
Fall asleep in Mama 's arms
- The cold winter storm - The cold winter storm
- Stay far away from our house - Stay far away from our house
- Dark nights , go away - Dark nights , go away
- Hushaby , my baby - Stop .
Fall asleep in Mama 's arms
Stop !
Who the hell are you ?
I am the one who cries with you
when you shed blood .
What do you want from me ?
Pastor .
In total ,
how many girls do you think they 've killed ?
Look up .
It 's Jeong Na-han .
What did you do to Lee Geum-hwa ?
Answer me , Jeong Na-han !
Kim Je-seok fooled all of you .
Do you even realize what you 're doing ?
How many innocent kids have you killed ?
What do you want from me ?
Check the mark on the man whom you call Father .
He is the snake .
Kill him .
No .
Father is the light .
Father .
Say something , Father .
Please ?
Can you hear me ?
Say something like you used to . Please !
I 'm sorry , Father .
What brings you here at this hour ?
You might make him sicker .
At that girl 's house ,
there was her twin sister whose birth was never registered .
It seemed as if she had been waiting for me .
So ?
Did you just leave ?
She told me to go have a look .
She said I should check the mark .
What mark ?
Six fingers .
Gwangmok .
That 's what the snake 's tongue does .
The tongue has fooled you .
Come with me . There 's something I 'd like to show you .
I heard monks used to give elephants to kings as gifts in ancient India .
Look at that elephant 's eyes .
What do you feel ?
They just ...
look cold .
Fearing elephants ' eyes is a sign
that you have an evil heart .
Monks in India gifted the kings with these creatures
so that the kings could look into their eyes every day .
The whole thing , including shipping , cost us 90 million won .
Take your time and wait for your salvation .
Why ...
Why aren 't you afraid of elephants ?
Kim Je-seok .
Are you really the man who became a god ?
I heard you 're real .
I heard you 're a god .
Then you shouldn 't be bedridden like this .
Finally , we found it .
Don 't go .
It 's dangerous .
My dear Myeong-hui .
You 've aged a lot .
STUDENT RECORDS
The sound of the horn Echoes all over the world
Jesus ' glories
When I blow the horn , when I call Jesus
I hear his voice
I should just enlist in the army .
Yo-sep !
What pains you the most now
is the fact that the man whom you guys used to call Father
was nothing but a lifeless meat .
They were just
innocent kids born with pitiful fates .
There were no " snakes " to begin with .
You 're wrong .
I met one .
It told me to kill him .
Oh , boy . I 'm so sorry .
Jeez , what the heck . I can 't believe this happened .
Gosh , the road is so slippery .
Are you all right ? Are you hurt ?
God .
I 'm sorry .
We meet again .
Who are you , really ?
I 'm ...
Pastor Park , the crook buster .
FAR EASTERN RELIGION RESEARCH INSTITUTE PARK UNG-JAE
But I guess
I got the wrong person today .
No worries . You can just go .
You can 't leave like this . Call your insurance company .
Hey !
Hey , Pungsa Kim Je-seok !
Only few people got to meet him in person .
I heard only his closest disciples were allowed to meet with him .
Jeez , it was true .
The inextinguishable ...
Master ...
Light that doesn 't age .
Please kill me .
Thanks for all your hard work .
Really , thanks for everything .
The dragon turned into a snake .
I 'm getting a whiff of blood .
Who are you ?
Answer me . Who are you ?
Do not talk or move .
Your intestines and lungs are almost done for .
The man you boys called Father all your lives
was also my disciple who devoted his entire life to me .
You deceived me .
I am ...
the light .
You are the stars that protect me .
Do not be sad
about what you boys did .
To soldiers , killing is a patriotic act .
- Shut your mouth ! - Shush .
Time makes humans rush through their lives and die .
However ,
I won the race against time .
I am ...
- the inextinguishable light . - Shut the hell up .
There are
many things that I must do for this world from now on .
I must live .
I am giving you a chance .
Beast .
Serve me .
No , you are just a predator who is desperate to live .
You shouldn 't have done that .
- Those kids did nothing wrong . - You don 't understand .
Those girls cry every night .
Have you even heard their cries ?
You can 't understand .
Slitting your throat a hundred times won 't be enough .
The sad eyes
will twist the snake 's neck .
Slitting your throat a hundred times won 't be enough !
Everything will be turned upside down .
The earth will become the sky ,
and the sky will become the earth .
The wise one .
Grab the snake 's foot .
I cannot
die by your hand here .
The snake will burn up in flames .
- And finally , - And finally ,
- dharma will be achieved . - dharma will be achieved .
Yes , it 's ...
That 's right . Right after the tunnel .
Yes .
Oh , I see .
A car flipped over and caught on fire .
Yes .
Yes , okay . Please hurry .
Okay , got it .
I ...
Forensics should ...
Okay , got it .
We heard from Lee Geum-hwa . She 's fine .
- Okay . - But apparently ,
she had a twin sister whose birth was never registered .
That girl died .
Gosh .
Pastor .
Yes ?
What did he say in his final moments ?
Who ?
Jeong Na-han .
It looked like he was saying something .
Well ...
He said he was cold .
Where are you ?
Have you forgotten about us ?
Why do you keep shedding tears with your face covered ?
Wake up .
Listen to our cries and sighs .
Get up .
Save us from evil with your mercy
and listen to our prayers .
Subtitle translation by Hyun-joo Choi